<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<useCaseModel name="user-view.target.v20071129">
		<useCase>
			<id>UC_01</id>
			<name>Opening TaRGeT</name>
			<description>This use case describes how the TaRGeT should behave when it is started up.</description>
			
			<flow>
				<description>Start up the TaRGeT.</description>
				<fromSteps>START</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1M</stepId>
					<action>Start the TaRGeT.</action>
					<condition>The .NET and Java runtime environment are installed in the machine (see requirements for further information about Java and .NET versions) [ER_TARGET_0015, ER_TARGET_0020, ER_TARGET_0025]</condition>
					<response>A splash screen is displayed. Verify the requirements document to check the splash screen. [FR_TARGET_0220]</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>2M</stepId>
					<action>Wait some seconds.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The TaRGeT is started. No TaRGeT project is opened. A background image is displayed (see requirements document for more details). [FR_TARGET_0225]</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
			<flow>
				<description>The .NET runtime environment is not installed in the machine.</description>
				<fromSteps>START</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1A</stepId>
					<action>Try to start the TaRGeT.</action>
					<condition>Java runtime environment is installed in the machine. The .NET runtime environment is not installed in the machine (see requirements for further information about Java and .NET versions). [ER_TARGET_0020, ER_TARGET_0025]</condition>
					<response>A message is displayed informing that an error has occurred and asking the user to see the log file. [FR_TARGET_0230]</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
			<flow>
				<description>The Java runtime environment is not installed in the machine.</description>
				<fromSteps>START</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1B</stepId>
					<action>Try to start the TaRGeT.</action>
					<condition>The Java runtime environment is not installed in the machine (see requirements for further information about Java version). [ER_TARGET_0020]</condition>
					<response>A message is displayed informing that no JRE is installed. The TaRGeT is not started up. [FR_TARGET_0230]</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
		</useCase>
		<useCase>
			<id>UC_05</id>
			<name>Creating a Project from Blank Work Area</name>
			<description>This use case describes the creation of a TaRGeT project when no project is opened.</description>
			
			<flow>
				<description>Create a new project when no project is opened.</description>
				<fromSteps>START</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1M</stepId>
					<action>Go to “File” option in the menu bar.</action>
					<condition>The TaRGeT is already started up. No project is opened.</condition>
					<response>The “New Project” option is enabled in the drop down menu. The Close Project option is disabled.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>2M</stepId>
					<action>Select the “New Project” option. [FR_TARGET_0020]</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The “New Project” screen is displayed. The default project name is displayed in the “Project Name” field. The default project location is displayed in the “Destination Folder” field.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>3M</stepId>
					<action>Click on “Finish” button.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>A progress bar is displayed. A new project work area is displayed. The project folder is created in the specified location.[FR_TARGET_0010]</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
			<flow>
				<description>Type a valid project name.</description>
				<fromSteps>2M</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>3M</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1A</stepId>
					<action>Type a valid project name. [FR_TARGET_0025]</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The “Project Name” field is filled.</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
			<flow>
				<description>Cancel the project creation.</description>
				<fromSteps>2M, 1A, 1C</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1B</stepId>
					<action>Click on the “Cancel” button.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The tool goes back to the window it was before the project creation.</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
			<flow>
				<description>Browse the destination folder.</description>
				<fromSteps>2M, 1A</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>3M</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1C</stepId>
					<action>Browse and select the location in which the project shall be created.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The “Destination Folder” field is filled.</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
			<flow>
				<description>Type an invalid project name.</description>
				<fromSteps>2M</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1D</stepId>
					<action>Type an invalid project name (e.g. with one of the following characters). [FR_TARGET_0025]</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>A message is displayed indicating that some characters are not allowed. The “Finish” button is disabled.</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
			<flow>
				<description>No project name is typed.</description>
				<fromSteps>2M</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1E</stepId>
					<action>Type a blank project name.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>A message is displayed indicating that a name must be specified. The “Finish” button is disabled.</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
			<flow>
				<description>Project directory already exists.</description>
				<fromSteps>2M</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1F</stepId>
					<action>Type a valid project name.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The “Project Name” field is filled.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>2F</stepId>
					<action>Browse and select the location in which there is a directory with the same name of the project.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The “Destination Folder” field is filled.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>3F</stepId>
					<action>Click on “Finish” button.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>A dialog is displayed indicating that the project folder already exists. The dialog asks if the user you want to proceed and erase all content of the folder.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>4F</stepId>
					<action>Click on “Yes” button.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>All the folder contents is deleted and the new project is created.</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
			<flow>
				<description>to create the project and delete all folder contents.</description>
				<fromSteps>3F</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1G</stepId>
					<action>Click on “No” button.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The focus goes back to the “New Project” window.</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
		</useCase>
		<useCase>
			<id>UC_10</id>
			<name>Creating a Project from an Already Opened Project</name>
			<description>This use case describes the creation of a TaRGeT project when a project is opened.</description>
			
			<flow>
				<description>Create a new project when a project is opened.</description>
				<fromSteps>START</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>UC_05#3M</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1M</stepId>
					<action>Go to “File” option in the menu bar.</action>
					<condition>The TaRGeT is already started up. A project is already opened.</condition>
					<response>The “New Project” option is enabled in the drop down menu.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>2M</stepId>
					<action>Select the “New Project” option. [FR_TARGET_0020]</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>A dialog box is displayed informing that the current project will be closed in order to create a new one.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>3M</stepId>
					<action>Click on “Yes” button.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The current project is closed. The “New Project” screen is displayed. The default project name is displayed in the “Project Name” field. The default project location is displayed in the “Destination Folder” field.</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
			<flow>
				<description>Click on “No” button.</description>
				<fromSteps>2M</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1A</stepId>
					<action>Click on “No” button.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The popup is closed and the tool goes back to the main window with the previous project opened.</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
		</useCase>
		<useCase>
			<id>UC_15</id>
			<name>Closing a Project</name>
			<description>This use case describes how the TaRGeT behaves while closing a project.</description>
			
			<flow>
				<description>Close a project.</description>
				<fromSteps>START</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1M</stepId>
					<action>Go to “File” option in the menu bar.</action>
					<condition>TaRGeT is started up and a project is already opened.</condition>
					<response>The “Close Project” option is enabled.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>2M</stepId>
					<action>Select the “Close Project” option. [FR_TARGET_0035]</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>A message is displayed asking if the user really wants to close the project.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>3M</stepId>
					<action>Click on “Yes” button.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The project is closed. The blank project area is displayed. The background image is shown. [FR_TARGET_0225]</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
			<flow>
				<description>Cancel the project closing.</description>
				<fromSteps>2M</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1A</stepId>
					<action>Click on “No” button.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The popup is closed and the tool goes back to the main window.</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
		</useCase>
		<useCase>
			<id>UC_20</id>
			<name>Opening an Existing Project from Blank Work Area</name>
			<description>This use case describes how the TaRGeT behaves while an existing project is opened by the user. This use case describes the project opening when no project is opened.</description>
			
			<flow>
				<description>Open an existing project from an empty work area.</description>
				<fromSteps>START</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1M</stepId>
					<action>Go to “File” option in the menu bar.</action>
					<condition>TaRGeT is already started up. No project is opened.</condition>
					<response>The “Open Project” option is enabled.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>2M</stepId>
					<action>Select the “Open Project” option. [FR_TARGET_0040]</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The “Open Project” window is displayed. No project is selected. The “Finish” button is disabled.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>3M</stepId>
					<action>Browse and select an existing project.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The “Project Name” field is now filled. The “Finish” button is enabled.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>4M</stepId>
					<action>Click on “Finish” button.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>A progress bar is displayed indicating that the selected existing project is being opened. After, the existing project is opened. The project work area is displayed.</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
			<flow>
				<description>Cancel the project opening.</description>
				<fromSteps>2M, 3M</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1A</stepId>
					<action>Click on “Cancel” button.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The tool goes to the blank work area. No project is opened.</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
		</useCase>
		<useCase>
			<id>UC_25</id>
			<name>Opening an Existing Project from an Already Opened Project</name>
			<description>This use case describes how the TaRGeT behaves while an existing project is opened by the user. It describes the project opening when a project is already opened.</description>
			
			<flow>
				<description>Open an existing project from an already opened project.</description>
				<fromSteps>START</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>UC_20#3M</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1M</stepId>
					<action>Go to “File” option in the menu bar.</action>
					<condition>TaRGeT is already started up. A project is already opened.</condition>
					<response>The “Open Project” option is enabled.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>2M</stepId>
					<action>Select the “Open Project” option. [FR_TARGET_0040]</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>A dialog box is displayed informing that the current project will be closed in order to open another one.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>3M</stepId>
					<action>Click on “Yes” button.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The “Open Project” screen is displayed.</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
			<flow>
				<description>Cancel the project opening.</description>
				<fromSteps>2M</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1A</stepId>
					<action>Click on “No” button.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The dialog box is closed and the current project work area is displayed.</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
		</useCase>
		<useCase>
			<id>UC_30</id>
			<name>Importing Valid Use Case Documents</name>
			<description>This use case describes how the TaRGeT shall behave when valid use case documents are imported to a project.</description>
			
			<flow>
				<description>Import a use case document.</description>
				<fromSteps>START</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1M</stepId>
					<action>Go to “Artifacts” option in the menu bar.</action>
					<condition>TaRGeT is started up. A project is already opened.</condition>
					<response>The “Import Use Case Documents” option is enabled.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>2M</stepId>
					<action>Select “Import Use Case Documents” option. [FR_TARGET_0100]</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The “Import Documents” window is displayed. The “Finish” button is disabled.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>3M</stepId>
					<action>Select “Add Document” button and browse a valid use case document. The document does not contain any interruption.</action>
					<condition>No document is imported.</condition>
					<response>The selected document path is inserted in the “Documents To Import” list. The “Finish” button is enabled.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>4M</stepId>
					<action>Click on “Finish” button.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>A progress bar is displayed indicating that the document(s) is (are) being processed and imported. [FR_TARGET_0110]</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>5M</stepId>
					<action>Wait the progress bar.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The imported document(s) is (are) placed in a specific folder and displayed in the “Artifacts” View. The imported use cases are displayed in the “Use Cases” View. [FR_TARGET_0010, FR_TARGET_0015]</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
			<flow>
				<description>Import another document.</description>
				<fromSteps>3M</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>4M</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1A</stepId>
					<action>Select “Browser” button and browse another valid use case document. The document must not have duplicated feature ids, when compared with the already browsed document.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The selected document path is inserted in the “Documents To Import” list.</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
			<flow>
				<description>Cancel the importing.</description>
				<fromSteps>2M, 3M, 1A</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1B</stepId>
					<action>Click on “Cancel” button.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The focus goes back to the project work area.</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
		</useCase>
		<useCase>
			<id>UC_31</id>
			<name>Importing a Use Case Document Containing Interruptions</name>
			<description>This use case describes how the TaRGeT shall behave when a use case document that contains an interruption specification is imported to a project.</description>
			
			<flow>
				<description>Imported Use Case Document contains one or more interruption specifications.</description>
				<fromSteps>UC_30#2M</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1M</stepId>
					<action>Select “Add Document” button and browse a use case document that contains at least one interruption.</action>
					<condition>There is no imported document.</condition>
					<response>The selected document path is inserted in the “Documents To Import” list. The “Finish” button is enabled.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>2M</stepId>
					<action>Click on “Finish” button.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>A progress bar is displayed indicating that the document is being processed. [FR_TARGET_0110]</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>3M</stepId>
					<action>Wait the progress bar.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The imported document(s) is (are) placed in a specific folder and displayed in the “Artifacts” View. The imported use cases and interruptions are displayed in the “Use Cases” View. [FR_TARGET_0010, FR_TARGET_0015]</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
			<flow>
				<description>Import another document that contains interruptions.</description>
				<fromSteps>1M</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>2M</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1A</stepId>
					<action>Select “Browser” button and browse another valid use case document. The document must contain one or more interruptions and features whose ids are different from those already browsed.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The selected document path is inserted in the “Documents To Import” list.</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
		</useCase>
		<useCase>
			<id>UC_35</id>
			<name>Importing a Use Case Document With Duplicated Feature ID</name>
			<description>This use case describes how the TaRGeT shall behave when a use case document with duplicated feature ID is imported to a project.</description>
			
			<flow>
				<description>Imported Use Case Document has duplicated feature ID.</description>
				<fromSteps>UC_30#2M</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1M</stepId>
					<action>Select “Add Document” button and browse a use case document with duplicated feature ID. This means that the document contains at least two features with the same ID. The document does not contain any interruption.</action>
					<condition>There is no imported document.</condition>
					<response>The selected document path is inserted in the “Documents To Import” list. The “Finish” button is enabled.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>2M</stepId>
					<action>Click on “Finish” button.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>A progress bar is displayed indicating that the document is being processed.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>3M</stepId>
					<action>Wait the progress bar. [FR_TARGET_0110]</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>An error dialog is displayed indicating the document that has duplicated ID and that the selected document(s) will not be imported. [FR_TARGET_0125]</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>4M</stepId>
					<action>Click on “OK” button.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The focus goes back to “Import Documents” window.</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
		</useCase>
		<useCase>
			<id>UC_36</id>
			<name>Importing a Use Case Document With Duplicated Interruption ID</name>
			<description>This use case describes how the TaRGeT shall behave when a use case document with duplicated interruption ID is imported to a project.</description>
			
			<flow>
				<description>Imported Use Case Document has duplicated interruption ID.</description>
				<fromSteps>UC_30#2M</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1M</stepId>
					<action>Select “Add Document” button and browse a use case document with duplicated interruption ID. This means that the document contains at least two interruptions with the same ID.</action>
					<condition>There is no imported document.</condition>
					<response>The selected document path is inserted in the “Documents To Import” list. The “Finish” button is enabled.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>2M</stepId>
					<action>Click on “Finish” button.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>A progress bar is displayed indicating that the document is being processed. [FR_TARGET_0110]</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>3M</stepId>
					<action>Wait the progress bar.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>An error dialog is displayed indicating the document that has duplicated ID and that the selected document(s) will not be imported. [FR_TARGET_0125]</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>4M</stepId>
					<action>Click on “OK” button.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The focus goes back to “Import Documents” window.</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
			<flow>
				<description>Imported Use Case Document has duplicated interruption ID with another one already imported.</description>
				<fromSteps>UC_30#2M</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1A</stepId>
					<action>Select “Add Document” button and browse a use case document with an interruption whose ID is the same of an already imported interruption.</action>
					<condition>There is an imported document with at least one interruption.</condition>
					<response>The selected document path is inserted in the “Documents To Import” list. The “Finish” button is enabled.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>2A</stepId>
					<action>Click on “Finish” button.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>A progress bar is displayed indicating that the document is being processed.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>3A</stepId>
					<action>Wait the progress bar. [FR_TARGET_0110]</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>An error dialog is displayed indicating the document that has duplicated ID and that the selected document(s) will not be imported.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>4A</stepId>
					<action>Click on “OK” button.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The focus goes back to “Import Documents” window.</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
		</useCase>
		<useCase>
			<id>UC_40</id>
			<name>Importing a Use Case Document With Duplicated Use Case ID</name>
			<description>This use case describes how the TaRGeT shall behave when a use case document with duplicated use case ID is imported to a project.</description>
			
			<flow>
				<description>Imported Use Case Document has duplicated use case ID.</description>
				<fromSteps>UC_30#2M</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1M</stepId>
					<action>Select “Add Document” button and browse a use case document with duplicated use case ID. This means that the document contains a feature that has at least two use cases with the same ID. The document does not contain any interruption.</action>
					<condition>No document is imported.</condition>
					<response>The selected document path is inserted in the “Documents To Import” list. The “Finish” button is enabled.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>2M</stepId>
					<action>Click on “Finish” button.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>A progress bar is displayed indicating that the document is being processed.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>3M</stepId>
					<action>Wait the progress bar. [FR_TARGET_0110]</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>An error dialog is displayed indicating the document that has duplicated use case ID and that the selected document(s) will not be imported. [FR_TARGET_0125]</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>4M</stepId>
					<action>Click on “OK” button.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The focus goes back to “Import Documents” window.</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
		</useCase>
		<useCase>
			<id>UC_45</id>
			<name>Importing a Use Case Document With Invalid Structure</name>
			<description>This use case describes how the TaRGeT shall behave when a use case document with invalid structure is imported to a project.</description>
			
			<flow>
				<description>Imported Use Case Document has an invalid structure.</description>
				<fromSteps>UC_30#2M</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1M</stepId>
					<action>Select “Add Document” button and browse a use case document with invalid structure.</action>
					<condition>No document is imported.</condition>
					<response>The selected document path is inserted in the “Documents To Import” list. The “Finish” button is enabled.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>2M</stepId>
					<action>Click on “Finish” button.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>A progress bar is displayed indicating that the document is being processed.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>3M</stepId>
					<action>Wait the progress bar.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>An error dialog is displayed indicating the document that has an error and that the selected document(s) will not be imported. [FR_TARGET_0110]</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>4M</stepId>
					<action>Click on “OK” button.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The focus goes back to “Import Documents” window.</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
			<flow>
				<description>Import another document.</description>
				<fromSteps>1M</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>2M</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1A</stepId>
					<action>Click on “Add Document” button and browse another valid use case document.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The selected document path is inserted in the “Documents To Import” list.</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
			<flow>
				<description>Cancel the importing.</description>
				<fromSteps>4M</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1B</stepId>
					<action>Click on “Cancel” button.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The focus goes back to the project work area.</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
		</useCase>
		<useCase>
			<id>UC_50</id>
			<name>Importing a Use Case Document with an Empty Mandatory Field</name>
			<description>This use case describes how the TaRGeT shall behave when a use case document with an empty mandatory is imported to a project.</description>
			
			<flow>
				<description>Selected use case document has an empty mandatory field.</description>
				<fromSteps>UC_30#2M</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>UC_55#3M</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1M</stepId>
					<action>Select “Browser” button and browse a use case document with an empty mandatory field. The document does not contain any interruption.</action>
					<condition>No document is imported.</condition>
					<response>The selected document path is inserted in the “Documents To Import” list. The “Finish” button is enabled.</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
		</useCase>
		<useCase>
			<id>UC_55</id>
			<name>Importing a Use Case Document With Invalid Step ID References</name>
			<description>This use case describes how the TaRGeT shall behave when a use case document with invalid id references is imported to a project.</description>
			
			<flow>
				<description>The selected use case document contains invalid id references.</description>
				<fromSteps>UC_30#2M</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1M</stepId>
					<action>Select “Add Document” button and browse a use case document with invalid ID references. The document does not contain any interruption.</action>
					<condition>No document is imported.</condition>
					<response>The selected document path is inserted in the “Documents To Import” list. The “Finish” button is enabled.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>2M</stepId>
					<action>Click on “Finish” button.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>A progress bar is displayed indicating that the document is being processed.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>3M</stepId>
					<action>Wait the progress bar.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>A warning message is displayed indicating that the document contains errors. The imported document is placed in the documents folder and is displayed in the “Artifacts” View. The imported use cases are displayed in the “Use Cases” View. A special icon indicates the use cases with invalid references. Also the error view displays details about invalid id references and/or duplicated ids.  [FR_TARGET_0010, FR_TARGET_0015, FR_TARGET_0110, FR_TARGET_0120]</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
			<flow>
				<description>Import another valid document.</description>
				<fromSteps>1M</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>2M</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1A</stepId>
					<action>Select “Add Document” button and browse another valid use case document. The document does not contain any interruption.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The selected document path is inserted in the “Documents To Import” list.</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
		</useCase>
		<useCase>
			<id>UC_56</id>
			<name>Importing a Use Case Document With Invalid Step ID References in Interruptions</name>
			<description>This use case describes how the TaRGeT shall behave when a use case document with invalid id references is imported to a project.</description>
			
			<flow>
				<description>The selected use case document contains invalid id references in an interruption.</description>
				<fromSteps>UC_30#2M</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1M</stepId>
					<action>Select “Add Document” button and browse a use case document with invalid ID references in an interruption.</action>
					<condition>No document is imported.</condition>
					<response>The selected document path is inserted in the “Documents To Import” list. The “Finish” button is enabled.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>2M</stepId>
					<action>Click on “Finish” button.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>A progress bar is displayed indicating that the document is being processed.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>3M</stepId>
					<action>Wait the progress bar.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>A warning message is displayed indicating that the document contains errors. The imported document is placed in the documents folder and is displayed in the “Artifacts” View. The imported interruptions are displayed in the “Use Cases” View. A special icon indicates the interruptions with invalid references. Also the error view displays details about invalid id references and/or duplicated ids.  [FR_TARGET_0010, FR_TARGET_0015, FR_TARGET_0110, FR_TARGET_0120]</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
		</useCase>
		<useCase>
			<id>UC_60</id>
			<name>Importing a Use Case Document With Duplicated Step IDs</name>
			<description>This use case describes how the TaRGeT shall behave when a use case document with duplicated step IDs is imported to a project.</description>
			
			<flow>
				<description>The selected use case document contains duplicated ids.</description>
				<fromSteps>UC_30#2M</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>UC_55#2M, UC_55#1A</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1M</stepId>
					<action>Select “Browser” button and browse a use case document with duplicated step ids. The document contains at least two steps in a use case with the same ID. The document does not contain any interruption.</action>
					<condition>No document is imported.</condition>
					<response>The selected document path is inserted in the “Documents To Import” list. The “Finish” button is enabled.</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
		</useCase>
		<useCase>
			<id>UC_61</id>
			<name>Importing a Use Case Document With Duplicated Step IDs in Interruptions</name>
			<description>This use case describes how the TaRGeT shall behave when a use case document with duplicated step IDs in interruptions is imported to a project.</description>
			
			<flow>
				<description>The selected use case document contains duplicated ids in an interruption.</description>
				<fromSteps>UC_30#2M</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>UC_56#2M</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1M</stepId>
					<action>Select “Browser” button and browse a use case document with duplicated step ids in an interruption. The document contains at least two steps in an interruption with the same ID.</action>
					<condition>No document is imported.</condition>
					<response>The selected document path is inserted in the “Documents To Import” list. The “Finish” button is enabled.</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
		</useCase>
		<useCase>
			<id>UC_63</id>
			<name>Importing a Use Case Document with a Feature Already Imported.</name>
			<description>This use case describes how the TaRGeT shall behave when a use case document is imported to a project and another use case document is already imported and the documents have at least one feature with same name and ID.</description>
			
			<flow>
				<description>Import a use case document when another use case document is already imported. The use case documents have at least one common feature with same ID and name.</description>
				<fromSteps>UC_30#2M</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1M</stepId>
					<action>Select “Add Document” button and browse a valid use case document. The document and the already imported document have at least one common feature with same ID and name and the use cases IDs are different. Both documents do not contain any interruption.</action>
					<condition>There is at least one valid document imported in the project. The document does not contain any interruption.</condition>
					<response>The “Import Documents” window is displayed. The “Finish” button is enabled.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>2M</stepId>
					<action>Click on “Finish” button.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>A progress bar is displayed indicating that the document(s) is (are) being processed and imported. [FR_TARGET_0110]</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>3M</stepId>
					<action>Wait the progress bar.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The imported document is placed in a specific folder and displayed in the “Artifacts” view. The imported use cases are displayed in the “Use Cases” view. The feature icon in the “Use Cases” view shows that the feature was merged. [FR_TARGET_0010, FR_TARGET_0015]</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
			<flow>
				<description>Import a use case document when another use case document is already imported. The use case documents have at least one common feature with same ID and different names.</description>
				<fromSteps>UC_30#2M</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1A</stepId>
					<action>Select “Add Document” button and browse a valid use case document. The document and the already imported document have at least one common feature with same ID but different names and the use cases IDs are different.</action>
					<condition>There is at least one valid document imported in the project.</condition>
					<response>The “Import Documents” window is displayed. The “Finish” button is enabled.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>2A</stepId>
					<action>Click on “Finish” button.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>A progress bar is displayed indicating that the document(s) is (are) being processed and imported. [FR_TARGET_0110]</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>3A</stepId>
					<action>Wait the progress bar.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The imported document is placed in a specific folder and displayed in the “Artifacts” View. The imported use cases are displayed in the “Use Cases” View. The feature icon in the “Use Cases” view shows that the feature was merged. A new warning is displayed in the “Error” view indicating that the features have same ID but different names. [FR_TARGET_0010, FR_TARGET_0015]</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
			<flow>
				<description>Import a document that contains a feature with same ID of another feature that belongs to a previously imported document.</description>
				<fromSteps>UC_30#2M</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1B</stepId>
					<action>Select “Add Document” button and browse a valid use case document. The document and the already imported document have at least one common feature with same ID. The features have at least one use case with same ID. [FR_TARGET_0125]</action>
					<condition>There is at least one valid imported document.</condition>
					<response>The selected document path is inserted in the “Documents To Import” list.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>2B</stepId>
					<action>Click on “Finish” button.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>A progress bar is displayed indicating that the document is being processed.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>3B</stepId>
					<action>Wait the progress bar. [FR_TARGET_0110]</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>An error dialog is displayed indicating the document has duplicated use case ID and that the selected document(s) will not be imported.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>4B</stepId>
					<action>Click on “OK” button.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The focus goes back to “Import Documents” window.</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
		</useCase>
		<useCase>
			<id>UC_65</id>
			<name>Viewing Use Case Documents with Microsoft Word</name>
			<description>This use case describes how use case documents can be viewed in TaRGeT with the Microsoft Word.</description>
			
			<flow>
				<description>Double-click on the document.</description>
				<fromSteps>START</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1M</stepId>
					<action>Double-click on a use case document in the “Artifacts” view.</action>
					<condition>A project is opened in TaRGeT. The project has at least one imported document.</condition>
					<response>The Microsoft Word is invoked and the document is opened. [FR_TARGET_0005]</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
		</useCase>
		<useCase>
			<id>UC_70</id>
			<name>Viewing Valid Use Case in HTML Format</name>
			<description>This use case describes how the TaRGeT use cases can be viewed in HTML format.</description>
			
			<flow>
				<description>View valid use case documents in HTML format in the main panel, by double-clicking the use case.</description>
				<fromSteps>START</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1M</stepId>
					<action>Double-click on a use case in the “Use Cases” view.</action>
					<condition>A project is opened in TaRGeT. The project has at least one imported valid use case document.</condition>
					<response>The selected Use Case is displayed in HTML format in the main panel. [FR_TARGET_0130]</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
			<flow>
				<description>View use case documents in HTML format in the main panel, by right-clicking the use case.</description>
				<fromSteps>START</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1A</stepId>
					<action>Right-click on a use case in the “Use Cases” view.</action>
					<condition>A project is opened in TaRGeT. The project has at least one imported valid use case document.</condition>
					<response>A drop down menu is displayed with two options.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>2A</stepId>
					<action>Select “Open with default view” option.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The selected Use Case is displayed in HTML format in the main panel. [FR_TARGET_0130]</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
			<flow>
				<description>View use case documents in HTML format in the default browser, by right-clicking the use case.</description>
				<fromSteps>1A</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1B</stepId>
					<action>Select “Open with default browser” option.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The selected Use Case is displayed in HTML format in the default browser. [FR_TARGET_0130]</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
		</useCase>
		<useCase>
			<id>UC_71</id>
			<name>Viewing Invalid Use Case in HTML Format</name>
			<description>This use case describes how the TaRGeT use cases can be viewed in HTML format when they have some error.</description>
			
			<flow>
				<description>View use case documents with duplicated step ID in HTML format in the main panel, by double-clicking the use case.</description>
				<fromSteps>START</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1M</stepId>
					<action>Double-click on a use case with duplicated step ID in the “Use Cases” view.</action>
					<condition>A project is opened in TaRGeT. The project has at least one imported use case with duplicated step ID.</condition>
					<response>The selected Use Case is displayed in HTML format in the main panel. The duplicated steps IDs are highlighted.   [FR_TARGET_0130]</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
			<flow>
				<description>View use case documents with invalid step ID reference in HTML format in the main panel, by right-clicking the use case.</description>
				<fromSteps>START</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1A</stepId>
					<action>Right-click on a use case with invalid step ID reference in the “Use Cases” view.</action>
					<condition>A project is opened in TaRGeT. The project has at least one imported use case with invalid step ID reference.</condition>
					<response>A drop down menu is displayed with two options.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>2A</stepId>
					<action>Select “Open with default view” option.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The selected Use Case is displayed in HTML format in the main panel. The invalid step ID reference is highlighted. [FR_TARGET_0130]</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
			<flow>
				<description>View use case documents with empty mandatory fields in HTML format in the default browser, by right-clicking the use case.</description>
				<fromSteps>1A</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1B</stepId>
					<action>Select “Open with default browser” option.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The selected Use Case is displayed in HTML format in the default browser. [FR_TARGET_0130]</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
		</useCase>
		<useCase>
			<id>UC_72</id>
			<name>Viewing Valid Interruption in HTML Format</name>
			<description>This use case describes how the interruptions can be viewed in HTML format.</description>
			
			<flow>
				<description>View valid interruptions in HTML format in the main panel, by double-clicking the use case.</description>
				<fromSteps>START</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1M</stepId>
					<action>Double-click on an interruption in the “Use Cases” view.</action>
					<condition>A project is opened in TaRGeT. The project has at least one imported valid use case document that contains interruptions.</condition>
					<response>The selected interruption is displayed in HTML format in the main panel. [FR_TARGET_0131]</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
			<flow>
				<description>View interruptions in HTML format in the main panel, by right-clicking the use case.</description>
				<fromSteps>START</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1A</stepId>
					<action>Right-click on an interruption in the “Use Cases” view.</action>
					<condition>A project is opened in TaRGeT. The project has at least one imported valid use case document that contains interruptions.</condition>
					<response>A drop down menu is displayed with two options.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>2A</stepId>
					<action>Select “Open with default view” option.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The selected interruption is displayed in HTML format in the main panel. [FR_TARGET_0131]</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
			<flow>
				<description>View interruptions in HTML format in the default browser, by right-clicking the use case.</description>
				<fromSteps>1A</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1B</stepId>
					<action>Select “Open with default browser” option.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The selected interruption is displayed in HTML format in the default browser. [FR_TARGET_0131]</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
		</useCase>
		<useCase>
			<id>UC_75</id>
			<name>Viewing a Generated Test Suite with Microsoft Excel</name>
			<description>This use case describes how the generated test suite documents can be viewed in TaRGeT with the Microsoft Excel.</description>
			
			<flow>
				<description>Double-click on the document.</description>
				<fromSteps>START</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1M</stepId>
					<action>Double-click on a test suite document in the “Artifacts” view.</action>
					<condition>A project is opened in TaRGeT. The project has at least one already generated test suite.</condition>
					<response>The Microsoft Excel is invoked and the document is opened. [FR_TARGET_0005]</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
		</useCase>
		<useCase>
			<id>UC_80</id>
			<name>Renaming a Document</name>
			<description>This use case describes how test suite and use case documents are renamed in TaRGeT.</description>
			
			<flow>
				<description>Rename a test suite document.</description>
				<fromSteps>START</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1M</stepId>
					<action>Right-click on a generated test suite document in the “Artifacts” view. [FR_TARGET_0001]</action>
					<condition>A project is opened in TaRGeT. The project has at least one already generated test suite.</condition>
					<response>A drop down menu is displayed.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>2M</stepId>
					<action>Click on “Rename” option in the drop down menu.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>A dialog is popped up with a text field.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>3M</stepId>
					<action>Change the document name to a valid name and click on “OK” button. [FR_TARGET_0025]</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The document is renamed.</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
			<flow>
				<description>Rename a use case document.</description>
				<fromSteps>START</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>2M</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1A</stepId>
					<action>Right-click on a use case document in the “Artifacts” view. [FR_TARGET_0001]</action>
					<condition>A project is opened in TaRGeT. The project has at least one imported use case document.</condition>
					<response>A drop down menu is displayed.</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
			<flow>
				<description>Select to rename more than one document.</description>
				<fromSteps>START</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1E</stepId>
					<action>In the “Artifacts” view, Select more than one document and right-click on the selection. [FR_TARGET_0001]</action>
					<condition>A project is opened in TaRGeT. The project has at least two documents (test suite or use case documents).</condition>
					<response>A drop down menu is displayed. The “Rename” option is disabled.</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
			<flow>
				<description>Type an invalid document name.</description>
				<fromSteps>2M</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1B</stepId>
					<action>Try to change the document name to an invalid name (e.g. a name containing . [FR_TARGET_0025]</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>A message is displayed indicating that the name is invalid. The “OK” button is disabled.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>2B</stepId>
					<action>Click on “Cancel” button.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The focus goes back to the main window.</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
			<flow>
				<description>Type a document name that is being used by another document.</description>
				<fromSteps>START</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>2B</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1C</stepId>
					<action>Right-click on a use case document in the “Artifacts” view. [FR_TARGET_0001]</action>
					<condition>A project is opened in TaRGeT. The project has at least  two test suites or two use case.</condition>
					<response>A drop down menu is displayed. The “Rename” option is enabled.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>2C</stepId>
					<action>Click on “Rename” option in the drop down menu.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>A dialog is popped up with a text field.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>3C</stepId>
					<action>Type a name that is already in use.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>A message is displayed indicating that the name is already in use. The “OK” button is disabled.</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
			<flow>
				<description>Type an empty name.</description>
				<fromSteps>2M</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>2B</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1D</stepId>
					<action>Type an empty name.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>A message is displayed indicating that the name must not be empty. The “OK” button is disabled.</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
		</useCase>
		<useCase>
			<id>UC_85</id>
			<name>Deleting a Document</name>
			<description>This use case describes how test suite and use case documents are deleted in TaRGeT.</description>
			
			<flow>
				<description>Delete a test suite document.</description>
				<fromSteps>START</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1M</stepId>
					<action>Right-click on a generated test suite document in the “Artifacts” view. [FR_TARGET_0003]</action>
					<condition>A project is opened in TaRGeT. The project has at least one already generated test suite.</condition>
					<response>A drop down menu is displayed.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>2M</stepId>
					<action>Click on “Delete” option in the drop down menu.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>A dialog is displayed asking a confirmation.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>3M</stepId>
					<action>Click on “Yes” button.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The document is deleted.</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
			<flow>
				<description>Delete a use case document that is not referred by another document.</description>
				<fromSteps>START</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1B</stepId>
					<action>Right-click on a use case document in the “Artifacts” view. [FR_TARGET_0003]</action>
					<condition>A project is opened in TaRGeT. The project has at least one imported use case document. The imported documents do not refer to a use case of another imported document.</condition>
					<response>A drop down menu is displayed.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>2B</stepId>
					<action>Click on “Delete” option in the drop down menu.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>A dialog is displayed asking a confirmation.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>3B</stepId>
					<action>Click on “Yes” button.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The document is deleted. The project work area is refreshed. [FR_TARGET_0015]</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
			<flow>
				<description>Delete a use case document that is referred by another document.</description>
				<fromSteps>START</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1C</stepId>
					<action>Right-click on a use case document in the “Artifacts” view. The selected document is referred by a use case of another imported document. [FR_TARGET_0003]</action>
					<condition>A project is opened in TaRGeT. The project has at least two imported use case documents. A use case is referred by another use case from a different document.</condition>
					<response>A drop down menu is displayed.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>2C</stepId>
					<action>Click on “Delete” option in the drop down menu.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>A dialog is displayed asking a confirmation and informing that the document is being referred by another document.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>3C</stepId>
					<action>Click on “Yes” button.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The document is deleted. The project work area is refreshed. Some invalid reference errors are displayed in “Error” view. [FR_TARGET_0015, FR_TARGET_0120]</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
			<flow>
				<description>Delete more than one generated test suite.</description>
				<fromSteps>START</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1D</stepId>
					<action>In the “Artifacts” view, Select more than one test suite document and right-click on the selection. [FR_TARGET_0003]</action>
					<condition>A project is opened in TaRGeT. The project has at least two generated test suites.</condition>
					<response>A drop down menu is displayed.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>2D</stepId>
					<action>Click on “Delete” option in the drop down menu.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>A dialog is displayed asking a confirmation.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>3D</stepId>
					<action>Click on “Yes” button.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The documents are deleted.</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
			<flow>
				<description>Delete one test suite and one use case document that is being referenced.</description>
				<fromSteps>START</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1E</stepId>
					<action>In the “Artifacts” view, Select one test suite document and a use case document, and right-click on the selection. [FR_TARGET_0003]</action>
					<condition>A project is opened in TaRGeT. The project has at least two imported use case document and at least one generated test suite. The imported use case document is referenced by another imported document.</condition>
					<response>A drop down menu is displayed.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>2E</stepId>
					<action>Click on “Delete” option in the drop down menu.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>A dialog is displayed asking a confirmation and informing that one of the selected use case documents is being referred by another document.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>3E</stepId>
					<action>Click on “Yes” button.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The documents are deleted.</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
			<flow>
				<description>Delete two use case documents. One document refers to the other.</description>
				<fromSteps>START</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1F</stepId>
					<action>In the “Artifacts” view, Select one test suite two use case documents, and right-click on the selection. One of the selected documents refers to the other. [FR_TARGET_0003]</action>
					<condition>A project is opened in TaRGeT. The project has two imported use case document. One imported use case document is referenced by the other.</condition>
					<response>A drop down menu is displayed.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>2F</stepId>
					<action>Click on “Delete” option in the drop down menu.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>A dialog is displayed asking a confirmation. No dialog must be displayed informing that there are selected documents being referenced.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>3F</stepId>
					<action>Click on “Yes” button.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The documents are deleted.</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
			<flow>
				<description>Cancel the document deletion.</description>
				<fromSteps>2M, 2B, 2C, 2D</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1A</stepId>
					<action>Click on “No” button.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The document(s) is (are) not deleted.</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
		</useCase>
		<useCase>
			<id>UC_90</id>
			<name>Updating the Use Case Documents outside the TaRGeT UI</name>
			<description>This use case describes how use case documents are updated outside TarGeT UI.</description>
			
			<flow>
				<description>Fix a use case document with duplicated step ID outside TaRGeT UI.</description>
				<fromSteps>START</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1M</stepId>
					<action>Open an already imported use case document with the Microsoft Word (outside the TaRGeT). The document has a duplicated step ID.</action>
					<condition>TaRGeT is started up and a project is opened. There is at least one imported use case document with duplicated step ID in the project.</condition>
					<response>The document is opened in the default viewer outside the TaRGeT.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>2M</stepId>
					<action>Fix the duplicated ID, save the document and close it.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The document is fixed.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>3M</stepId>
					<action>Go back to the TaRGeT window.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>A progress bar is displayed while the project is being refreshed</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>4M</stepId>
					<action>Wait the progress bar.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The fixed duplicated ID error is removed from the “Error” view.</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
		</useCase>
		<useCase>
			<id>UC_95</id>
			<name>Rejecting a Damaged Use Case Documents</name>
			<description>This use case describes how use case documents are rejected after their structure is damaged.</description>
			
			<flow>
				<description>Damage an imported use case document.</description>
				<fromSteps>START</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1M</stepId>
					<action>Double-click on a use case document in the “Artifacts” view.</action>
					<condition>A project is opened in TaRGeT. There is one imported and valid use case document.</condition>
					<response>The Microsoft Word is invoked and the document is opened. [FR_TARGET_0005]</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>2M</stepId>
					<action>Change the document, damaging its structure, and go back to the TaRGeT window.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>A progress bar is displayed while the project is being refreshed.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>3M</stepId>
					<action>Wait the progress bar.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>A new error is displayed in the “Error” view indicating that the document is damaged. No information related to this document is displayed in the “Use Case” view. An error icon is assigned to the document in the “Artifacts” view. [FR_TARGET_0015, FR_TARGET_0120, FR_TARGET_0125]</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
		</useCase>
		<useCase>
			<id>UC_100</id>
			<name>Rejecting a Use Case Document With Duplicated Feature ID</name>
			<description>This use case describes how use case documents are rejected after assigning to a feature an ID that is being used by a feature of another document.</description>
			
			<flow>
				<description>Assign to a feature an ID that is being used by a feature of another document.</description>
				<fromSteps>START</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1M</stepId>
					<action>Double-click on a use case document in the “Artifacts” view.</action>
					<condition>A project is opened in TaRGeT. There is two imported and valid use case document.</condition>
					<response>The Microsoft Word is invoked and the document is opened. [FR_TARGET_0005]</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>2M</stepId>
					<action>Change the document, by assigning to a feature an ID that is being used by a feature of another document, and go back to the TaRGeT window.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>A progress bar is displayed while the project is being refreshed.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>3M</stepId>
					<action>Wait the progress bar.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>A new error is displayed in the “Error” view indicating that one of the documents contains a duplicated feature ID. The document is rejected and no information related to the document is displayed in the “Use Case” view. An error icon is assigned to the document in the “Artifacts” view. [FR_TARGET_0015, FR_TARGET_0120, FR_TARGET_0125]</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
		</useCase>
		<useCase>
			<id>UC_105</id>
			<name>Rejecting a Use Case Document With Duplicated Use Case ID</name>
			<description>This use case describes how use case documents are rejected after assigning to a use case an ID that is being used by another use case of the same feature.</description>
			
			<flow>
				<description>Assign to a feature an ID that is being used by a feature of another document.</description>
				<fromSteps>START</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1M</stepId>
					<action>Double-click on a use case document in the “Artifacts” view.</action>
					<condition>A project is opened in TaRGeT. There is one imported and valid use case document. The document has at least one feature with more than one use case.</condition>
					<response>The Microsoft Word is invoked and the document is opened. [FR_TARGET_0005]</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>2M</stepId>
					<action>Change the document, by assigning to a use case an ID that is being used by another use case of the same feature, and go back to the TaRGeT window.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>A progress bar is displayed while the project is being refreshed.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>3M</stepId>
					<action>Wait the progress bar.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>A new error is displayed in the “Error” view indicating that one of the documents contains a duplicated use case ID. The document is rejected and no information related to the document is displayed in the “Use Case” view. An error icon is assigned to the document in the “Artifacts” view. [FR_TARGET_0015, FR_TARGET_0120, FR_TARGET_0125]</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
		</useCase>
		<useCase>
			<id>UC_106</id>
			<name>Searching for Use Cases</name>
			<description>This use case describes how to search for use cases within TaRGeT.</description>
			
			<flow>
				<description>Perform a search when some valid use case documents are already imported.</description>
				<fromSteps>START</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1M</stepId>
					<action>Choose “Tools” option in the menu bar.</action>
					<condition>TaRGeT is started up. A project is already opened. There is at least one document imported. No error is listed in the “Error” list.</condition>
					<response>A drop down menu is displayed. “Search” option is available.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>2M</stepId>
					<action>Choose “Search” option in the drop down menu.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>“Search” window is displayed. [FR_TARGET_0135]</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>3M</stepId>
					<action>Type a query in the input area.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The “Find” field is filled.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>4M</stepId>
					<action>Click on “Search” button.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The search results are displayed in "Search Results" View. Verify if the results are in accordance to the query. [FR_TARGET_0135]</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
			<flow>
				<description>Cancel the search.</description>
				<fromSteps>3M</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1A</stepId>
					<action>Click on “Cancel” button.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The focus goes back to the work area.</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
			<flow>
				<description>Perform a search using the specific field “Use Case Identifier”.</description>
				<fromSteps>2M</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1B</stepId>
					<action>...ust be contained in the project.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The “Find” field is filled.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>2B</stepId>
					<action>Click on “Search” button.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>At least one use case is displayed in “Search Results” View.  [FR_TARGET_0135]</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
			<flow>
				<description>Perform a search using the specific field “From Step”.</description>
				<fromSteps>2M</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>4M</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1C</stepId>
					<action>Type “fromstep:START” in the input area.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The “Find” field is filled.</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
		</useCase>
		<useCase>
			<id>UC_107</id>
			<name>Viewing Search Results</name>
			<description>This use case describes how the search result can be viewed within TaRGeT.</description>
			
			<flow>
				<description>View found use case documents in HTML format by double-clicking the use case.</description>
				<fromSteps>UC_106#4M</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1M</stepId>
					<action>Double-click on a use case in the “Search Results” view.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The selected Use Case is displayed in HTML format in the main panel.</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
		</useCase>
		<useCase>
			<id>UC_110</id>
			<name>Generating Test Suites</name>
			<description>This use case describes how the test suites are generated within TaRGeT.</description>
			
			<flow>
				<description>Generate test cases by requirements.</description>
				<fromSteps>START</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1M</stepId>
					<action>Choose “Tools” option in the menu bar.</action>
					<condition>The TaRGeT is already started up. A project is opened and some use cases are already imported. No error is listed in the “Error” list.</condition>
					<response>A drop down menu is displayed. “Test Generation” option is available.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>2M</stepId>
					<action>Choose “Generate Test Suite” option in the drop down menu.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The “Test Generation” window is displayed. The “Requirements Selection” page is displayed, showing all requirements referred in the valid imported documents. [FR_TARGET_0140]</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>3M</stepId>
					<action>Select some requirements (not all). [FR_TARGET_0145]</action>
					<condition>The imported use cases have more than one step which refers to distinct requirements.</condition>
					<response>Some requirements are selected.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>4M</stepId>
					<action>Click on “Finish” button.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>A progress bar is displayed. [FR_TARGET_0155]</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>5M</stepId>
					<action>Wait the generation processing.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>A dialog box is displayed indicating that the generation is completed. The dialog box also summarizes the generation process. [FR_TARGET_0160]</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>6M</stepId>
					<action>Click on “OK” button.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The test suite is generated with the default name and the correct structure. The new test suite is in “Artifacts” view in a specific folder. Verify that the requirements traceability matrix is generated. Verify that the generated test cases are only related to the selected requirements. [FR_TARGET_0010, FR_TARGET_0170, FR_TARGET_0175, FR_TARGET_0180]</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
			<flow>
				<description>Try to generate tests with errors in the project.</description>
				<fromSteps>START</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1G</stepId>
					<action>Choose “Tools” option in the menu bar.</action>
					<condition>The TaRGeT is already started up. A project is opened and some use case documentation is already imported. There is at least one error is listed in the “Error” list.</condition>
					<response>A drop down menu is displayed. “Test Generation” option is available.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>2G</stepId>
					<action>Choose “Generate Test Suite” option in the drop down menu.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>A dialog is displayed indicating that there are errors in the project. [FR_TARGET_0140]</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
			<flow>
				<description>Cancel the generation.</description>
				<fromSteps>3M</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1A</stepId>
					<action>Click on “Cancel” button.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The focus goes back to the work area.</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
			<flow>
				<description>All requirements are selected.</description>
				<fromSteps>2M</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1B</stepId>
					<action>Click on “Select All” button. [FR_TARGET_0145]</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>All listed requirements are selected. “Finish” button is enabled.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>2B</stepId>
					<action>Click on “Finish” button.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>A dialog box is displayed informing that even though all requirements were selected, all scenarios might not be covered by the test cases.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>3B</stepId>
					<action>Click on “OK” button.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>A progress bar is displayed. [FR_TARGET_0155]</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>4B</stepId>
					<action>Wait the generation processing.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>A dialog box is displayed indicating that the generation is completed. The dialog box also summarizes the generation process. [FR_TARGET_0160]</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>5B</stepId>
					<action>Click on “OK” button.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The test suite is generated with the default name and the correct structure (see requirements). The new test suite is in “Artifacts” view in a specific folder. Verify that the requirements traceability matrix is generated. [FR_TARGET_0010, FR_TARGET_0170, FR_TARGET_0175, FR_TARGET_0180]</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
			<flow>
				<description>Generate all test cases.</description>
				<fromSteps>2M</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1D</stepId>
					<action>Choose "Tools" option in the menu bar.</action>
					<condition>The TaRGeT is already started up. A project is opened and some use cases are already imported. No error is listed in the "Error" list.</condition>
					<response>A drop down menu is displayed. "Test Generation" option is available.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>2D</stepId>
					<action>Choose "Generate Test Suite" option in the drop down menu.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The "Test Generation" window is displayed. The "Requirements Selection" page is displayed, showing all requirements referred in the valid imported documents. [FR_TARGET_0140]</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>3D</stepId>
					<action>Click on “Finish” button.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>A progress bar is displayed. [FR_TARGET_0155]</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>4D</stepId>
					<action>Wait the generation processing.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>A dialog box is displayed indicating that the generation is completed. The dialog box also summarizes the generation process. [FR_TARGET_0160]</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>5D</stepId>
					<action>Click on “OK” button.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The test suite is generated with the default name and correct structure (see requirements). It contains all the use case scenarios. The new test suite is in “Artifacts” view in a specific folder. Verify that the requirements traceability matrix is generated. [FR_TARGET_0010, FR_TARGET_0170, FR_TARGET_0175, FR_TARGET_0180]</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
			<flow>
				<description>There is no reference to any requirement in the imported use cases.</description>
				<fromSteps>1M</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1E</stepId>
					<action>Choose “Test Generation” option in the drop down menu.</action>
					<condition>No requirement is referenced in the imported use cases.</condition>
					<response>The Test Generation window is displayed. The “Requirements List” is disabled. The “Select All” and “Deselect All” buttons are disabled.</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
			<flow>
				<description>Deselect All” button is clicked.</description>
				<fromSteps>3M</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1F</stepId>
					<action>Click on “Deselect All” button.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>No requirement is selected.</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
		</useCase>
		<useCase>
			<id>UC_115</id>
			<name>Generating Test Suites with Test Purposes</name>
			<description>This use case describes how the test suites are generated using test purposes within TaRGeT.</description>
			
			<flow>
				<description>Generate test cases using one test purpose composed of one step.</description>
				<fromSteps>UC_110#2M</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1M</stepId>
					<action>Select some requirements. [FR_TARGET_0145]</action>
					<condition>The imported use cases have more than one step which refers to distinct requirements.</condition>
					<response>Some requirements are selected.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>2M</stepId>
					<action>Go to “Test Purpose Creation” page.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The “Test Generation” page is displayed, showing a combo box with all steps that can be used to define the test purposes. The “Finish” button is enabled.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>3M</stepId>
					<action>Select a step in the steps list and click on “Select” button.</action>
					<condition>Path coverage is set to 100.</condition>
					<response>The selected step is copied to the “Current Test Purpose” field.  [FR_TARGET_0151]</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>4M</stepId>
					<action>Click on “OK” button.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The test purpose is added to the “Created Test Purposes” list. The “Current Test Purpose” is empty.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>5M</stepId>
					<action>Click on “Finish” button.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>A progress bar is displayed. [FR_TARGET_0155]</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>6M</stepId>
					<action>Wait the generation processing.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>A dialog box is displayed indicating that the generation is completed. The dialog box also summarizes the generation process. [FR_TARGET_0160]</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
			<flow>
				<description>Generate test cases using two test purposes.</description>
				<fromSteps>3M</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>4M</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1A</stepId>
					<action>Select a different step in the steps list and click on “Select” button.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The selected step is copied to the “Current Test Purpose” field.  [FR_TARGET_0151]</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
			<flow>
				<description>Clear the current test purpose field.</description>
				<fromSteps>1A</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1B</stepId>
					<action>Click on “Clean” button on “Current Test Purpose” area.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The “Current Test Purpose” field is empty.</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
			<flow>
				<description>Remove a test purpose from the created test purposes list.</description>
				<fromSteps>4M</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1C</stepId>
					<action>Select a test purpose on “Created Test purposes” list.</action>
					<condition>There is at least one test purpose on the “Created Test purposes” list.</condition>
					<response>The test purpose is highlighted.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>2C</stepId>
					<action>Click on “Clean” button on “Created Test Purposes” area.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The test purpose was removed from the “Created Test Purposes” list.</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
			<flow>
				<description>Remove all test purposes from the created test purposes list.</description>
				<fromSteps>4M</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1D</stepId>
					<action>Click on “Clear All” button on “Created Test Purposes” area.</action>
					<condition>There is more than one test purpose on “Test purposes” list.</condition>
					<response>The “Created Test Purposes” list is empty.</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
			<flow>
				<description>Path coverage percentage is 50%.</description>
				<fromSteps>4M</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>5M</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1F</stepId>
					<action>Set path coverage to 50.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>“Path Coverage” is 50%. [FR_TARGET_0152]</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
		</useCase>
		<useCase>
			<id>UC_120</id>
			<name>Generating Test Suites by Use Cases</name>
			<description>This use case describes how the test suites are generated in order to cover some selected use cases.</description>
			
			<flow>
				<description>Generate test cases by use cases.</description>
				<fromSteps>UC_110#2M</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1M</stepId>
					<action>Go to “Use Cases Selection” page.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The “Use Case Selection” page is displayed, showing the use cases grouped by features.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>2M</stepId>
					<action>Select at least one use case in the list and click on “Add Use Case” button.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The selected use case is copied to the “Selected Use Cases” list. [FR_TARGET_0153]</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>3M</stepId>
					<action>Click on “Finish” button.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>A progress bar is displayed. [FR_TARGET_0155]</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>4M</stepId>
					<action>Wait the generation processing.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>A dialog box is displayed indicating that the generation is completed. The dialog box also summarizes the generation process. Verify if the generated test cases cover the selected use cases. [FR_TARGET_0160]</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
			<flow>
				<description>Remove selected use cases.</description>
				<fromSteps>2M</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1A</stepId>
					<action>Select at least one use case from the “Selected Use Cases” list.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The selected use cases are removed from the list.</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
		</useCase>
		<useCase>
			<id>UC_125</id>
			<name>Generating Test Suites With Interruptions</name>
			<description>This use case describes how the test suites are generated from use cases that are embedded by interruptions.</description>
			
			<flow>
				<description>Generate test cases with interruptions.</description>
				<fromSteps>UC_110#2M</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1M</stepId>
					<action>Go to “Interruption Assignment” page.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The “Interruption Assignment” page is displayed, showing the use case steps grouped by use cases and features. The “Interruptions” list and “Steps - Interruptions” list are displayed.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>2M</stepId>
					<action>Select an interruption in the “Interruptions” list. Select a step to which the interruption will be linked and click on “Link” button.</action>
					<condition>There is at least one interruption in the documents.</condition>
					<response>The link between the selected interruption and step is added into “Step - Interruptions” list. [FR_TARGET_0146]</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>3M</stepId>
					<action>Click on “Finish” button.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>A progress bar is displayed. [FR_TARGET_0155]</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>4M</stepId>
					<action>Wait the generation processing.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>A dialog box is displayed indicating that the generation is completed. The dialog box also summarizes the generation process. Verify if the test cases were correctly generated with interruption information. [FR_TARGET_0160]</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
			<flow>
				<description>Link again an interruption to a step.</description>
				<fromSteps>2M</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>3M</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1A</stepId>
					<action>Select an interruption in the “Interruptions” list. Select a different step to which the interruption will be linked and click on “Link” button.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>A new link between the selected interruption and step is added into “Step - Interruptions” list.</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
			<flow>
				<description>Remove link between an interruption to a step.</description>
				<fromSteps>2M</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1B</stepId>
					<action>Select a link in the “Steps - Interruptions” list and click on “Remove” button.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The selected link is removed from “Steps - Interruptions” list.</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
			<flow>
				<description>Remove all interruption - step links.</description>
				<fromSteps>1A</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1C</stepId>
					<action>Click on “Remove All” button.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>All links are removed from “Steps - Interruptions” list.</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
		</useCase>
		<useCase>
			<id>UC_130</id>
			<name>Generating Test Suites Changing Test Case Field Parameters</name>
			<description>This use case describes how the user can parameterize the test case fields.</description>
			
			<flow>
				<description>Changing “Objective prefix” parameter.</description>
				<fromSteps>START</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1M</stepId>
					<action>Open the properties file, change the “tcg.objective_prefix” parameter, and save the properties file.</action>
					<condition>TaRGeT application is closed.</condition>
					<response>The properties file is changed. [FR_TARGET_0175]</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>2M</stepId>
					<action>Run TaRGeT application, and open a project that contains valid imported documents.</action>
					<condition>There is an already created project with at least one imported use case.</condition>
					<response>The TaRGeT is started up, and the project is opened.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>3M</stepId>
					<action>Open the “Test Suite Generation” wizard and generate some tests.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The test suite is generated. The test cases contain its objective field with the pre-defined prefix.</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
			<flow>
				<description>Changing “Empty Field” parameter.</description>
				<fromSteps>START</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1A</stepId>
					<action>Open the properties file, change the “tcg.empty_field” parameter, and save the properties file.</action>
					<condition>TaRGeT application is closed.</condition>
					<response>The properties file is changed. [FR_TARGET_0175]</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>2A</stepId>
					<action>Run TaRGeT application, and open a project that contains valid imported documents.</action>
					<condition>There is an already created project with at least one imported use case.</condition>
					<response>The TaRGeT is started up, and the project is opened.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>3A</stepId>
					<action>Open the “Test Suite Generation” wizard and generate some tests.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The test suite is generated. The test cases contain all its empty fields now filled with the content defined by the parameter.</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
			<flow>
				<description>Changing “Test Case Id” parameter to a fixed value.</description>
				<fromSteps>START</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1B</stepId>
					<action>Open the properties file, change the “tcg.tescase_id” parameter to a fixed value, and save the properties file.</action>
					<condition>TaRGeT application is closed.</condition>
					<response>The properties file is changed. [FR_TARGET_0175]</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>2B</stepId>
					<action>Run TaRGeT application, and open a project that contains valid imported documents.</action>
					<condition>There is an already created project with at least one imported use case.</condition>
					<response>The TaRGeT is started up, and the project is opened.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>3B</stepId>
					<action>Open the “Test Suite Generation” wizard and generate some tests.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The test suite is generated. The test cases id now shall be exactly that one specified in the properties file.</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
			<flow>
				<description>Changing “Test Case Id” parameter to a value that changes accordingly to its id.</description>
				<fromSteps>START</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1C</stepId>
					<action>Open ...</action>
					<condition>TaRGeT application is closed.</condition>
					<response>The properties file is changed. [FR_TARGET_0175]</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>2C</stepId>
					<action>Run TaRGeT application, and open a project that contains valid imported documents.</action>
					<condition>There is an already created project with at least one imported use case.</condition>
					<response>The TaRGeT is started up, and the project is opened.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>3C</stepId>
					<action>Open the “Test Suite Generation” wizard and generate some tests.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The test suite is generated. The test cases id now shall contain an incremental number as specified in the properties file.</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
			<flow>
				<description>Changing “Test Case Id” parameter to a value that contains an incremental id and the feature id.</description>
				<fromSteps>START</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1D</stepId>
					<action>Open the properties file, change the  Save the properties file.</action>
					<condition>TaRGeT application is closed.</condition>
					<response>The properties file is changed. [FR_TARGET_0175]</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>2D</stepId>
					<action>Run TaRGeT application, and open a project that contains valid imported documents.</action>
					<condition>There is an already created project with at least one imported use case.</condition>
					<response>The TaRGeT is started up, and the project is opened.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>3D</stepId>
					<action>Open the “Test Suite Generation” wizard and generate some tests.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>The test suite is generated. The test cases id now shall be started by the feature Id and finished by an incremental number as specified in the properties file.</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
		</useCase>
		<useCase>
			<id>UC_135</id>
			<name>Viewing the About Window</name>
			<description>This use case describes how the about window is displayed.</description>
			
			<flow>
				<description>Access the about window.</description>
				<fromSteps>START</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1M</stepId>
					<action>Choose “Help” option in the menu bar.</action>
					<condition>The TaRGeT is already started up.</condition>
					<response>A drop down menu is displayed.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>2M</stepId>
					<action>Choose “About TaRGeT” option in the drop down menu.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>“About” window is displayed. The content of the windows is detailed in TaRGeT requirements document. [FR_TARGET_0210]</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
		</useCase>
		<useCase>
			<id>UC_140</id>
			<name>Viewing the Help Window</name>
			<description>This use case describes how the about window is displayed.</description>
			
			<flow>
				<description>Access the help window.</description>
				<fromSteps>START</fromSteps>
				<toSteps>END</toSteps>
				<step>
					<stepId>1M</stepId>
					<action>Choose “Help” option in the menu bar.</action>
					<condition>The TaRGeT is already started up.</condition>
					<response>A drop down menu is displayed.</response>
				</step>
				<step>
					<stepId>2M</stepId>
					<action>Choose “Help Contents” option in the drop down menu.</action>
					<condition/>
					<response>“Help” window is displayed. [FR_TARGET_0205]</response>
				</step>
			</flow>
		</useCase>
</useCaseModel>
